<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Admission</string>
    <string name="content_description">Description</string>
    <string name="text_splash_screen">Learn to Serve</string>
    <string name="text_login_email">Enter email</string>
    <string name="text_login_password">Enter Password</string>
    <string name="text_open">Open</string>
    <string name="text_close">Close</string>


    <string name="message">Facilitating Superior Human Beings was our initiative behind inception of the Superior College Lahore. We always wanted to create a difference in people’s lives through our passionate contributions. Our students are a valuable human capital of Pakistan and we dreamt of making students superior by inculcating in them sense of purpose, innovation and creativity, teamwork, excellence, and rewards for performance. These values give our students true essence of life, success and immortality."
            </string>

    <string name="history">Our history is overwhelmed with Superior values which are depicted in every initiative we have taken. Facilitating superior human beings was the initiative behind the inception of Superior College Lahore

“The dream of Prof. Dr. Chaudhry Abdul Rehman of educated and energetic Pakistan drove him to establish Superior University Lahore.”

We started off from the core values and, with dedication and hard work, we have come a long way.

With over 250 campuses all around the country, we strive hard every day to achieve our mission. Our efforts of making Superior University recognized by well-reputed international educational institutions led us to this time when we have more than hundred universities on board with us from across the globe.

We feel safe to say that Superior University is now considered to be one of the best universities in Pakistan.</string>

    <string name="rules">"Concurrent admission at any other institution is not allowed.\n
Admission obtained on false documentation is liable to dis­ciplinary action.\n
Students must be respectful to the faculty, administrative staff and fellow students.\n
Any political activity or indecent behavior in or around the cam­pus is a punishable offense.\n
Students must carry ID cards on the campuses and at Superior functions.\n
All students are required to must fol­low the dress code. No makeup assignments, quiz­zes are al­lowed after due dates, unless permission is granted from concerned teacher."
            </string>

    <string-array name="name">
        <item>Muhammad Riaz</item>
        <item>Naveed Ur Rehman</item>
        <item>Sohaib Mehmood</item>
        <item>Husnain H Tarar</item>
        <item>Nabeel ur Rehman</item>
        <item>Yasir Khan</item>
        <item>Shahzada Suneel</item>
        <item>Chaudhry Muhammad Yousaf</item>
        <item>Sanawar K Awan</item>
        <item>Saleem Mughal</item>
        <item>Saqib Imran</item>
        <item>Hamid Younas</item>
        <item>Tariq Awan</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="designation">
        <item>Project Director The Superior Group</item>
        <item>Project Director Lahore Zone</item>
        <item>Director Marketing</item>
        <item>General Manager (GM) Business</item>
        <item>Director Academics</item>
        <item>Regional Director Multan Zone</item>
        <item>Regional Director Mianwali Zone</item>
        <item>Regional Director Faisalabad Zone</item>
        <item>Regional Director Shahkot Zone</item>
        <item>Regional Director Gujranwala Zone</item>
        <item>Regional Director Okara Zone</item>
        <item>Regional Director Sargodha Zone</item>
        <item>Regional Director Sialkot Zone</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="message">
        <item>At Superior we are committed to transform lives of our students providing them unique learning environment with superior values of creativity innovation, team work, agility, fairness and excellence. The student success matters to us the most. Their educational LAURELS in professional and Personal life will surely make them discover their Superior selves these optimistic patriotic individuals create a difference as they turn every obstacle into an opportunity their journey of Academic Excellence means our Superiority of winning hearts of the People.</item>
        <item>Our Superior Team is a blend of creativity, dedicated, hardworking and focused individuals who have ability to do the impossible for us NOTHING is IMPOSSIBLE in the world to do.</item>
        <item>The idea to be Superior is a mindset and to attain it you have to be excellent enough to create uniqueness and add value in the lives of many. We are in pursuit of reaching a paradigm where Superior means The ONLY ONE.</item>
        <item>The years of learning at Superior develops a habit to be optimistic. The positive mindset creates every obstacle into an opportunity and gives you a brighter picture about the life.</item>
        <item>To be the best you have to prove yourself that “ You are the only 1” the team Superior is destined to create an emotional intelligence generation really to impact positivity among our youth our Academic laurels have made us synonymous to our name. So be Superior.</item>
        <item>Honour and fame can only become your identity if you if you run after your dreams Superior Group of Colleges envision your bright future and helps you attain it with grace and courage.</item>
        <item>Who you are tomorrow begins with what you are today Superior makes you work to believe in your abilities and create an identity which remains with you throughout your life.</item>
        <item>At Superior we make you go wholeheartedly to do anything in order to achieve, something worth having. We give direction and purpose to your efforts. Your years with us will surely make you a Super hero and gentleman in life.</item>
        <item>At the Superior we make sure that time is always right to do what is right. One good thing about us is that when we prepare you to be the best we make sure you become the one.</item>
        <item>Education at Superior is a beautiful experience. It makes you fall in love with the environment of togetherness. The discussions conversations, talks laugh are those techniques which replace your empty or null mind with a superior One.</item>
        <item>Your years at Superior are the most exciting moments of every student. We teach you that the key to a Successful life “to SCHEDULE YOUR PRIORITIES”. Excellence waits for you.</item>
        <item>Superior Success is about what you inspire other to do. We always encourage our students to BE THE REAL the world will adjust. The co-curricular activities @ Superior provide a platform to create a difference with their personality. Choose Superior to be Superior.</item>
        <item>Superior Group of colleges with its Vision is creating a positive impact. Our Plan IQ and EQ are strengthening the future of Pakistan. Join us to be the master of your own fate.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="activitiesName">
        <item>Learning and Entertainment Together</item>
        <item>Industrial Tours</item>
        <item>Recreational Tours</item>
        <item>Student Excellence Award</item>
        <item>Sports and Cultural Festival Superior Galas</item>
        <item>Awards For Annual Programs</item>
        <item>Quizzes</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="activitiesText">
        <item>Superior Cultural and Sports Festivals are the hallmark of Superior annual mega events organized in all the Superior Colleges campuses. To maximize opportunities for learning through entertainment, we have 16 other events been organized frequently throughout the year. The interactive and co curricular learning techniques.</item>
        <item>The present era is the age of practical know-how and Superior Group of Colleges offers an ample opportunity to its students through visits to successful industries and top-class business organizations like Nestle, Packages, ICI, Dawood Hercules, Millet Tractors, Haier Electronics and other leading firms and companies that add value to their practical skills.</item>
        <item>Seeking meaningful pleasure is natural to human beings. This refreshes the mind, lessens the stress, dilutes tension and smoothes out worries. To that end, field tours to Murree, Swat and Kalam are arranged throughout the academic sessions, allowing leisure breaks to academic monotony. These excursions are greatly applauded by ‘Superior’ parents.</item>
        <item>Special awards are introduced as a token of encouragement for promising students. In order to endorse and foster the deserving, uplift their morale and motivate them to achieve more, students are given full or partial tuition fee concessions on the basis of their academic performance. This encouragement not only promotes our vision of facilitating ‘Superior Human Beings’ but also creates competition among students. Through this competition we make our students believe in Almighty Allah’s promise that, “Man gets whatever he strives for”. Further to encourage brilliant students we offer need-based as well as merit scholarships and special cash prizes for their outstanding performance.</item>
        <item>One of the most memorable events at ‘Superior’ is Cultural Day when students of all disciplines put on traditional cultural dresses and represent the rich culture of Punjab. Campuses of Superior Colleges are decorated to showcase styles from typical Pakistani villages, reflecting genuine Punjabi Culture. Traditional Punjabi food is specially offered at different food stalls to provide real time cultural experience.This vibrant and memorable event reflects true excitement and entertainment which remains forever.</item>
        <item>We have a wide range of awards, cash and other fabulous prizes for our outstanding students on their meritorious academic achievements. We handsomely give out prizes in Inter and B.Com. Special prizes including gifts and computers are given to the toppers of class tests and the toppers of the college and college send-up examinations.Toppers of every class in send-ups are awarded college tracksuits and the overall toppers of send ups are awarded mobile phones.</item>
        <item>Quizzes are of two types: written and oral. They are administered on the basis of discussion and comprehension of students on every chapter. The aim of taking quizzes is to evaluate the students’ understanding of the course topics and discuss unresolved issues after assessment.One way in which every Superior student can get involved is by attending the Galas especially organized to appreciate growing abilities of students. For this, Welcome and Farewell functions are arranged, hereby students are encouraged to display their talents and show their artistry through well-conceived parodies, brilliant skits, fabulous mushaira, Qirat, Naat, symposia and academic quizzes.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="facilityName">
        <item>Computer Labs</item>
        <item>Science Labs</item>
        <item>Transport Facility</item>
        <item>Superior cafe</item>
        <item>Library</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="facilityText">
        <item>At every Superior College, we have purpose built modern labs for practicing the knowledge being leant. We have a keen emphasis on making our students know how the systems they read theoretically do work practically.To help our youth develop interest in IT and Computer Science, we have Computer Labs with latest versions of computers. Expert computer teachers and practitioners guide and train our students in proper usage.</item>
        <item>Superior Colleges have built modern Science Labs where students practice theories of Biology, Chemistry and Physics. Expert Lab Attendants and teachers help them do experiments and learn practical side of science subjects by applying the science formulas. We believe that these labs are the base house of future expert doctors, engineers and researchers. So we have provided latest equipment, training and practical facility and also hygienically safe and clean free labs.</item>
        <item>The Superior students are looked after with provision of modern, comfortable and well managed transport facility. We understand that public transportation facilities are not sufficient, comfortable and time bound which bothers students by extending their scheduled travel time. Thus, according to the city needs, number of coasters and buses of Superior Colleges run errands to pick and drop students.</item>
        <item>Café is always a place of refreshment and entertainment for having breaks during strenuous academic routine. The Superior Colleges Cafes are:
\n• Spacious and clean
\n• Well-lit and have variety of food items
\n• Having LCDs for students’ entertainment.</item>
        <item>A library is an integral part of any educational institution. Libraries at different campuses of Superior Group of Colleges have congenial and peaceful environment and are equipped with hundreds of books on different subjects i.e. Commerce, Business, Management, IT and Computer Science, Engineering and Literature, Reference Materials, Local and International Journals, Newspapers, Magazines etc.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="spinner_items">
        <item>Choose Scholarship Program</item>
        <item>Merit Based</item>
        <item>Needy Based</item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

</resources>
